salvagebid.com 2018-03-03

# Privacy Policy

Last updated on: November 17, 2014

Welcome! Thanks for using Salvagebid.com. By using Salvagebid's website, products, and services, you accept and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, so please read and review the terms below.

This Privacy Policy covers how Salvagebid, LLC and its subsidiaries ("Salvagebid") collects, uses, discloses, retains, and protects your personal information. This Privacy Policy covers only information that is collected through Salvagebid's website located at www.salvagebid.com and all related webpages and mobile versions ("Website"), services, phone support, email support, online chat support, products, content, applications, and tools (collectively "Services"). This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Salvagebid does not own or control, or to people that Salvagebid does not employ or manage.

**If you object to anything in this Privacy Policy, or otherwise do not understand or agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy, do not use Salvagebid's Services.** By using Salvagebid's Services, you agree to be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy. You may print a copy of this Privacy Policy by using the print button or feature in your browser. Salvagebid suggests retaining a copy for future reference.

Salvagebid may change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice to you. You agree that Salvagebid may provide you with notice of such changes in any of the following ways: by requiring you to acknowledge and accept the revised version at your next login, via email from Salvagebid, and/or by posting a change notice on Salvagebid's Website for a reasonably limited time. It is your responsibility to review any changes to this Privacy Policy. **If you object to any of the changes to this Privacy Policy, or otherwise do not understand or agree to any of the changes to this Privacy Policy, do not use Salvagebid's Services.** By continuing to access or use Salvagebid's Services following notice of any change to this Privacy Policy, you agree to and are bound by this Privacy Policy as changed.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and is part of the Salvagebid [Buyer Terms and Conditions](https://www.salvagebid.com/terms).

Salvagebid collects your personal information when you register with Salvagebid and when you use Salvagebid's Services. Salvagebid collects personal information from you and the devices (including mobile devices) you use to access Salvagebid's Services. Categories of personal information that Salvagebid collects includes without limitation: (a) identifying information such as your name, address, email address, phone number, and driver's license; (b) bidding, buying, selling, and other transaction information; (c) financial information such as credit card or bank account numbers; (d) other information you provide to Salvagebid through your use of Salvagebid's Services; and (e) other information Salvagebid is required or authorized by applicable law to collect to identify you or verify other information collected.

Salvagebid collects your personal information to (a) provide you with access to and use of Salvagebid's Services, (b) operate, improve, and personalize Salvagebid's Services, (c) contact you regarding your use of the Services, (d) provide you with customer service and support, (e) customize Salvagebid's advertising and marketing, and (f) to detect, prevent, and mitigate fraudulent or illegal activities.

Salvagebid automatically collects certain personal information from you and your devices (including mobile devices) and stores it in log files. Categories of personal information that Salvagebid collects in this manner include without limitation: (a) internet protocol (IP) addresses, (b) browser type, (c) internet service provider (ISP), (d) referring/exit pages, (e) operating system, (f) date/time stamp, and (g) clickstream data. Salvagebid uses this personal information and technologies such as beacons, tags and scripts to analyze trends, to administer Salvagebid's Services, to track your movements around the Website, and to gather demographic information about Salvagebid's member base as a whole.

Salvagebid may place a text file called a "cookie" in the browser files of your computer. The cookie itself does not contain personal information but it will enable Salvagebid to relate your use of this Website to personal information that you have specifically, voluntarily, and knowingly provided. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites. Salvagebid may use cookies to track your traffic patterns (as described above). In addition, Salvagebid uses encrypted cookies to authenticate your identity on each page after you log on to Salvagebid's Website. You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you have set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. Some of Salvagebid's Services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Salvagebid does not share your personal information with third-parties or nonaffiliated entities except in the following circumstances: (a) when Salvagebid has your permission or pursuant to your request; (b) to process or facilitate your purchase, sale, or shipment of any vehicle through Salvagebid's Services; (c) to state, federal, or other regulatory agencies as part of the title or ownership transfer process; (d) in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; (e) to establish or exercise Salvagebid's legal rights or defend against legal claims; (f) upon receipt of a written request from law enforcement; or (g) if Salvagebid reasonably believes that doing so is legally required or is in Salvagebid's best interest to protect its legal rights or the legal rights of others.

If Salvagebid is acquired by or merged with another company, to the extent permitted by applicable law, Salvagebid may transfer your personal information to such company. In this event, Salvagebid will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Salvagebid's Website is hosted in the United States. If you are visiting from the European Union or any other region with laws governing the collection and use of personal information that may differ from U.S. law, please note that you are transferring your personal information to the United States which does not have the same protections and/or laws as the EU and by providing your personal information you consent to: (a) the use of your personal information for the purposes identified herein and in accordance with this Privacy Policy; and (b) the transfer of your personal information to the United States as indicated herein and in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Salvagebid reserves the right to send you certain communications relating to Salvagebid's Services and your account with Salvagebid, including but not limited to notifications, service announcements, and administrative messages without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. Your access to and use of some or all of Salvagebid's Services may not be possible if you do not wish to receive these communications.

Salvagebid will retain your personal information as long as it is necessary and relevant to provide you with Salvagebid's Services. Additionally, Salvagebid will retain personal information from closed or cancelled member accounts to comply with legal and regulatory obligations, resolve disputes and claims, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, assist with any investigation, and enforce this Privacy Policy and the Salvagebid [Buyer Terms and Conditions](https://www.salvagebid.com/terms) and take any other actions permitted by law.

Salvagebid has physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your personal information. If Salvagebid learns of a security systems breach, Salvagebid may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. By using Salvagebid's Services or otherwise providing personal information to Salvagebid, you agree that Salvagebid can communicate with you electronically regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues relating to your use of Salvagebid's Services. Salvagebid may post a notice on Salvagebid's Website if a security breach occurs. Salvagebid may also send an email to you at the email address you have provided. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive free written notice of a security breach (or to withdraw your consent from receiving electronic notice) you should notify Salvagebid at [info@salvagebid.com](mailto:info@salvagebid.com).

Salvagebid takes your security seriously and takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information. However, no data transmission over the internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. The following is a summary of the measures Salvagebid takes to protect your personal information:

  * **Secure Socket Layer Encryption:  **Salvagebid uses Secure Socket Layer ("SSL") encryption when transmitting certain kinds of personal information, such as financial services information or payment information. An icon resembling a padlock is displayed on the bottom of most browsers window during SSL transactions that involve credit cards and other forms of payment. Any time Salvagebid asks you for a credit card number for payment or for verification purposes, it will be SSL encrypted. The information you provide will be stored securely on servers. Once you choose to store or enter your credit card number on Salvagebid, it will not be displayed back to you in its entirety when you retrieve or edit it in the future. Instead of the entire number, you will only see asterisks and either the first four digits or the last four digits of your number.
  * **Vendors and Partners:  **Salvagebid works with vendors and partners to protect the security and privacy of user information.
  * **Employee and Contractor Access to Information:  **Salvagebid limits access to your personal information to those employees who Salvagebid reasonably believes need to come into contact with that information to provide you with use of and access to Salvagebid's Services.
  * **Education and Training for Employees:  **Salvagebid has implemented a company-wide education and training program about security that is required of every Salvagebid employee.

If you have questions or concerns, please contact Salvagebid at:

Salvagebid, LLC  
6168 NE Hwy. 99, Ste. 201  
Vancouver, WA 98665 USA
